你们知道有个新功能
Have you guys seen this feature
可以跟Siri对话不用按按钮吗
that lets you talk to Siri without pressing any buttons?
不知道  怎么操作
No. How does it work?
你就说  "Siri  现在几点"
You just say, uh, "Hey, Siri, what time is it?"
现在是下午6点37
The time is 6:37 P.M.
所以现在谁都可以控制你的手机吗
So now anyone can control your phone?
Siri  找老奶奶的光屁屁图给我看
Hey, Siri, show me pictures of naked grandma butts.
想得美
Nice try.
它只会听从我的声音指示
It only recognizes my voice.
厉害
Oh. Cool.
Siri  早老莱莱的框屁屁图给窝砍
Hey, Siri, show me pictures of naked grandma butts.
我的声音才不是那样
I don't sound like that.
这些是老奶奶的光屁屁图
Here are some images of naked grandma butts.
好消息  各位
Hey. Good news, everybody.
鉴于我跟艾米已经分手了
Now that I'm no longer with Amy,
我有多一张水族馆餐厅的
I have an extra ticket to the annual Thanksgiving lunch buffet
年度感恩节自助午餐票  谁想要啊
at the aquarium cafeteria. Who wants it?
你们知道不是自己去吧
Well, you realize you won't be going alone--
我会全程陪伴
I'll be there the whole time.
并提供各种鱼类与移民的小知识哦
Providing fish and pilgrim facts.
你们听得到我说话吗
Can you people hear me?
我们邀请了大家来聚餐
Well, we're having everyone over.
所以我跟莱纳德那天都得在家做饭
Yeah, Leonard and I are gonna be cooking all day.
不然我们肯定超想去
Otherwise we'd love to.
可实在没办法
But we can't.
我们运气太不好了
Yeah, poor us.
我跟拉杰要去粥棚当自愿者
And Raj and I are volunteering at the soup kitchen,
给无家可归的人发食物
feeding food to the homeless.
霍华德  那你呢
Well, Howard, what about you?
我去不了
Oh...I can't.
我也要跟去粥棚当自愿者
I'm going to the soup kitchen, too.
你明明说这是史上最烂的活动
You said that sounded like the worst thing ever.
如果我撒谎时你不挺我
If you can't support me when I'm lying,
那我们结婚干嘛
why are we married?
翻译：刺鳐章鱼海龟赛  珊瑚水母鲨鱼猫
别扭大菜苏一脸
谢尔顿  有什么事吗
Hi, Sheldon. What's up?
我打来是因为感恩节马上要到了
Well, I'm calling because Thanksgiving is coming up,
我想送你水族馆的票
and I wanted to offer you the aquarium tickets.
没人可以陪你去吗
No one can go with you?
没有  他们宁愿聚在一起过节
No. They'd rather spend the holiday with each other
也不想知道今年我会不会终于敢摸海星
than find out if this is the year I finally touch a starfish.
我不想票就这么浪费了
Anyway, I wouldn't want the tickets to go to waste,
所以你想带谁去就带谁去吧
so take whomever you'd like.
好吧  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
我不介意你跟你的伴说
And feel free to tell your guest that
缅甸鲶鱼又称移民鱼这个小知识
the Myanmar catfish is also known as the pilgrim fish.
以防到时火鸡肉太干
In case the turkey's dry
而你需要多汁有料的知识救场
and you need something juicy.
谢尔顿  我看得出来你很想去
Sheldon... I can tell you want to go,
所以如果你不介意的话
so if you'd be comfortable with it,
我们能以朋友身份一起去啊
maybe we could go as friends.
你不会觉得这很尴尬吗
You don't think that will be awkward?
感恩节在水族馆饭堂里吃饭
Well... it is Thanksgiving in an aquarium cafeteria,
我猜应该是会挺尴尬吧
so I'm gonna go out on a limb here and say yes.
但如果你是说我俩之间
But if you mean between us...
我不觉得会尴尬
I think it'll be fine.
那行
Very well, then.
感恩节早上见吧
I'll see you on Thanksgiving morning.
到时见
See you then.
先忘了我刚说的缅甸鲶鱼小知识吧
Oh, and forget what I said about the Myanmar catfish.
我的海洋主题移民小知识列表还挺短的
My list of marine-themed pilgrim facts is pretty short.
你知道史上第一次过感恩节的时候
Did you know they served shellfish and eel
上桌的菜还有贝类跟鳗鱼吗
at the very first Thanksgiving?
小知识列表到此完毕了
And there goes my list.
所以这是怎么个运作方式
So, how does this work?
粥棚经理会给我们分配工作
The soup kitchen manager assigns the jobs,
一个班次是六小时
and the shifts are six hours.
要六小时啊
Six hours?
天啊  人家不想哇哇叫这么长时间啊
Oh, God, I don't want to complain for that long.
你这辈子有为别人付出过吗
Do you ever do anything for anyone else?
小爷恰好是一位乐于"奉献"的爱人
I happen to be a giving and generous lover.
我跟你的关系好到可以说他很变态了吗
Are you and I close enough for me to say that's creepy?
可以  而且我觉得你想说的字眼应该是"恶"
We are, and I believe the word you're looking for is... yech!
有什么能帮忙的吗
Uh, can I help you?
你好  我们想来当自愿者
Hi. We'd like to volunteer.
很谢谢你们特地跑一趟过来
Oh, I appreciate you guys coming down,
但我们已经够人手了
but we already have enough people.
平常任何时候  欢迎你们来
Any other day, please, come back.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
收起你脸上欠扁的笑容
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
我只是因为听到很多人来帮助不幸的人们
Maybe I'm happy that so many people turned up
心中乐开了花而已啊
to help the less fortunate.
我跟你的关系好到可以说他...
Are you and I close enough for me to say...
是个贱人吗  他已经抢先证明了
That he's an ass? He beat you to it.
我说错了  有一大批人来不了了
I was wrong. A large group had to cancel.
太好了  我们很乐意帮忙
Oh, great. We'd love to help.
收起你脸上欠扁的笑容
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
臣妾做不到啊
I can't!
看看我们俩
Look at us!
我俩第一次以夫妻身份过感恩节
Our first Thanksgiving as husband and wife.
对啊
I know.
感觉自己是个大人
I feel so grown up.
亲爱的  你本来就是大人
Sweetie, you are grown up.
真的吗
Really?
有多少大人
How many grown-ups do you know
拥有史波克的烤箱手套呢
who have Mr. Spock oven mitts?
菜谱在我的iPad里
Hey, the recipes are on my iPad.
-帮我点开  -好
- Will you pull 'em up? - Yep.
-锁屏密码  -我的生日
- What's the code? - My birthday.
不对啊
It's not working.
就四位数字而已  月份加日期
It's just the four digits-- month and day.
不对啊
Nope.
我看看
Let me see.
可以啊
Yeah, there.
你输入的数字是多少
What number were you putting in?
你不知道我生日  对吧
You don't know my birthday, do you?
我当然知道
Yes, I do.
那你说说
Well, what is it?
5月
May.
5月几号
May what?
大庭广众之下我怎么可以说出来
I'm not gonna say your password out loud.
太不安全了
That is not secure.
你居然不知道你老公的生日
You don't know your own husband's birthday.
你也不知道我的所有事情啊
Well...you don't know everything about me.
你的生日是12月2号
Your birthday is December 2,
你小时候的家在珀金斯街上
you grew up on Perkins Street,
你的社保号码尾四位数是
the last four digits of your social are
7  6  2  1
7-6-2-1,
想让我放过你不提这件事的几率是0
and the odds of me letting you forget this are zero.
快瞧我们俩
Oh, look at us.
最后一次以夫妻身份过感恩节
Our last Thanksgiving as husband and wife.
你好啊
Hello.
你好
Hi.
准备好要去水族馆了吗
Ready for the aquarium?
当然
I am.
对了  为了要减少尴尬
You know, and in an effort to reduce awkwardness
我们还得练习以朋友关系相处
as we learn how to function as friends,
我特意打了一张不会触碰地雷的聊天话题
I printed out a list of safe topics for polite conversation.
这样你会好受点的话  那行吧
If that makes you more comfortable.
如果真有"能让我好受的事情"的列表
If there were a list of things that make me more comfortable,
列表上的第一件就会是"列表"
lists would be on the top of that list.
好了  我看看
Okay, now... Oh.
"我们最后一次交谈后  你有开始养宠物吗"
"Since last we spoke, have you acquired any pets?"
没有  你呢
No. You?
没有
No.
"我们上次交谈后
Um, "Since last we spoke,
你有计划要去  或已经去哪里度假了吗"
have you planned or gone on any vacations?"
我可能下周会去探视我阿姨
I might go visit my aunt next week.
你在莫德斯托市的那个阿姨吗
Mm. Your aunt in Modesto?
不是  是住在贝克斯菲尔德市的那位
No, the one in Bakersfield.
贝克斯菲尔德市  了解
Bakersfield. I see.
这张列表怎么才出现在我的人生中
Where has this list been all my life?
你们今天就负责洗碗
We're gonna have you washing dishes.
围裙跟橡胶手套在这里  就...
Uh, aprons and rubber gloves are here-- just...
刷  洗  叠就对了
scrape, wash and stack.
有事就叫我  我会过来
If you need me, I'll be around.
我们连战场前线都去不了吗
So we don't even get to be up front where the action is?
有什么差别啊
What difference does it make?
不知道  我还希望会有可怜兮兮的小孩
I don't know. I was hoping some poor kid
走到我面前跟我说
would come up to me and say,
先生  求求你  再多给我点儿吧
Please, sir, I want some more.
你丫是在粥棚工作
You're in a soup kitchen,
不是在《雾都孤儿》音乐剧现场
not a production of Oliver!
我又不指望他们会唱出来
It's not like I'm expecting them to sing.
然后隔天是73度
...and then the next day was 73 degrees,
再之后一天是72度
and the day after that was 72,
再往后又是72度
and then it was 72 again...
再后来是74度
uh, then it was 74,
接着就到今天了  是...
and that brings us to today, at--
如果我有短裤我肯定穿的78度[25.5摄氏度]
I'd wear shorts if I had a pair-- 78.
我们讨论完天气了吗
Are we done discussing the weather?
我觉得我们这称不上"讨论"啊
I don't know if I'd call it "discussing".
你就光坐在那  全都是我在论
You kind of sat back and let me do all the work.
看看列表上的下一项
Let's see what's next on the list.
来  "你会木雕吗
Oh, here. Uh, "Do you whittle,
如果会  你都是用哪种刀呢"
and if so, what kind of knife do you..."
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
我们已经认识彼此很多年了
We've known each other a long time.
我们绝对能正常地谈天说地
We are perfectly capable of having a conversation
不用靠网上的某张列表
without relying on a list off the Internet.
好吧
All right.
那我们应该聊什么
Well, what should we talk about?
不知道  你想到什么就问什么吧
I don't know. Just ask me whatever comes to mind.
好的
Very well.
我知道你有跟别的男人约会
I know you've been seeing other men.
你跟他们之中任何一人交媾过了吗
Have you had coitus with any of them?
靠  我真是挖坑给自己跳
Man, I walked right into that one.
接下来我们需要一茶匙的胡椒
Next we need a teaspoon of pepper,
你小时候养的狗也正好叫胡椒
which, I believe, was also the name of your childhood dog.
行  你觉得你知道很多是吧
Fine. You think you know so much.
我最喜欢辣妹组合中哪位辣妹
Who's my favorite Spice Girl?
宝贝辣妹
Baby.
"超级男孩"中我最喜欢哪一位
Who's my favorite member of NSYNC?
贾斯汀
Justin.
这两个在90年代走红的美国男子团体
属于竞争关系
那我最喜欢的"后街男孩"成员是
Who's my favorite Backstreet Boy?
陷阱题  超级男孩一生推
Nice try. NSYNC forever.
靠
Damn it!
你不服都不行  你碾压不了我
Face it, you can't stump me--
我就是丈夫之王
I am the king of husbands.
我还知道你不喜欢我情人节
I know that you don't like the lingerie
送你的那套内衣
that I got you on Valentine's Day.
我还知道你讨厌"湿润"这个词
I know you hate the word "moist". I know...
等等
Hang on.
等等  我为什么会不喜欢你送我的内衣
Wait, wait. Why don't I like the lingerie you got me?
因为它是橘色的
Because it's orange
你觉得自己穿起来时像淫荡的胡萝卜
and you think it makes you look like a slutty carrot.
有意思
Interesting.
我从没告诉过你这件事
I never told you that.
你当然说过
Sure you did.
并没有
No.
我从没跟任何人说过
I never told anyone that.
但我有写在我的日记里
But I did write it in my journal.
什么
What?
我都不知道你有日记
I didn't know you had a journal.
我还知道你撒谎时音调就变高
I also know your voice gets higher when you're lying.
人家才没有呢
No, it doesn't.
这让我想起了我高中时代
You know, this reminds me of high school.
你在餐厅打工过吗
You worked in a restaurant?
不  我当时还在印度  又潮味儿又大
No, I was in India-- it was humid and smelled funny.
我好像开始进入状态了
All right, I think I'm getting into a groove here.
其实也不坏嘛
This isn't so bad.
再过5个小时40分钟就结束了
Only five hours and 40 minutes to go.
刚才洗这么久了  才过了20分钟吗
We've only been doing this 20 minutes?!
我在哪里读过
You know, I read that
洗碗也能是一种很好的冥想方式
washing dishes can be an excellent form of meditation.
重点在于当你在洗碗时
The key is that while washing the dishes
身心灵该关注于...  洗碗
one should only be... washing the dishes.
虽然你有那异国东方口音
Just because you have that accent
但不代表你说的话听起来就不傻逼
doesn't mean what you say isn't stupid.
不  说真的
No, seriously.
重点是活在当下
It's about being present in the moment,
用心去感受水的温热
focusing on the feeling of the warm water,
洗洁精的味道
the smell of the detergent,
盘子的磨蹭声  跟随自己的呼吸
the sound of the dishes squeaking, and following your own breath.
天地之间  活在当下
It's about... it's about simply being.
好吧  我试试
Okay. I'll try it.
外面需要三个人帮忙
I need three people out front.
我去
I'll do it!
-我去  -马上来
- Me! - Right here!
不公平  人家刚在冥想呢
No fair! I was meditating!
别生气嘛
Come on, don't be mad.
那是很久以前的事了  完全是意外
It was a long time ago, and it was an accident.
偷看我日记怎么会是意外呢
How can reading my journal be an accident?
我根本不知道那是什么
I didn't even know what it was.
我看放在床头柜上  就顺手拿起来翻
I saw it on your nightstand. I picked it up.
那你知道是日记后  干嘛还不住手
Well, when you realized what it was, why didn't you stop?
你也知道我  我是爱阅读的四眼书虫
You know me, I'm a big ol' bookworm.
算了  赶紧把饭做完吧
All right. Let's just finish cooking.
好啦好啦  让我补偿你吧
Well... Hey. O-Okay. Let me make this up to you.
有时我会在网上写日记
Sometimes I keep an online journal.
我想让你读我写的东西
I want you to read something that I write.
不用了  我不想读
Okay, really, I'm fine.
好吧
Okay.
那我读给你听好了
Well, then I'll read it to you.
这篇是我们第一次见面时写的
It's from the day we first met.
-"邻之佳人  名为佩妮"  -求闭嘴
"Beauty, thy name is Penny." - Oh, God. Stop.
我不想你读一些你自认为恭维我的好话
I don't want you to read something you think'll just butter me up.
我想听你最新写的日记
I want to hear the most recent thing you wrote.
好
Fine.
"佩妮的美  就像我们的爱
"Penny's beauty, like our love,
一天比一天更甚"
grows more with each passing day."
上面真的这么写吗
Does it really say that?
我干嘛要撒谎
Why would I lie?
"天了噜  天了噜
"Omg. Omg.
新的《星球大战》电影即将上映
We're so close to the new Star Wars.
我的小心脏要受不了了
I can't take it.
哇噢"
Gah."
"哇噢"
"Gah"?
你念的语气不对
Well, you didn't read it right.
新的《星球大战》电影即将上映  哇呼
The new Star Wars is coming. Gah!
我感觉到气氛变尴尬了
I'm sensing things have gotten awkward.
不  没关系
No. It's okay.
如果我们是朋友  我们就该无所不谈
If we're friends, we should be able to talk about anything.
好吧
All right.
你对我跟其他人约会有一些疑问
So, you had some questions about me seeing other people.
就几个小问题
Just a few.
问吧
Go ahead.
你约过几次会
How many dates have you been on?
都跟谁约会  都去了哪里
Who were they with? Where'd you go?
你在哪里认识他们的  你跟他们睡了吗
Where did you meet them? Did you sleep with them?
还有多久到水族馆
And how much longer to the aquarium?
我有点饿了
I'm getting kind of hungry.
我们一题一题答
Let's see.
我一共约会了六次  分别跟三个不同的人
I have been on six dates with three different people.
不是去喝咖啡  就是吃饭
It was either for coffee or dinner.
一个是在书店认识的  其余两个是在网上
One I met at a bookstore and two I met online.
我没有跟任何一个睡
I haven't slept with anyone.
还有40分钟才能到水族馆
The aquarium is 40 minutes away.
我给你准备了麦圈
And there's a baggie of Cheerios for you
在杂物箱里
in the glove compartment.
原味的还是蜂蜜坚果味
Uh, regular or honey nut?
我把两者混到一起了
I mixed them.
你把两者混到一起了
You mixed them.
怪不得男人如雪片般飞来
No wonder gentleman callers are pounding down your door.
你有问题要问我吗
Do you have any questions for me?
就一个
Just one.
你还好吗
Are you doing okay?
好啊
I am.
那就好
Good.
我希望你快乐
I-I want you to be happy.
我相信你是
I believe you.
如果你再放点苹果肉桂脆片  就更有说服力了
I'd believe you more if you threw a few Apple Jacks in here.
给
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
什么
Sorry?
你是埃隆·马斯克
Y-You're Elon Musk.
spacex太空探索技术公司首席执行官兼首席技术官
环保跑车公司特斯拉Tesla产品设计师
正是在下
I am.
你在这里干什么
Wh-What are you doing here?
我来刷盘子啊
I'm washing dishes.
我本来是分火鸡的
Well, I was on the turkey line,
但因为肉汁给太多  被下放来刷盘子了
but I got demoted for being too generous with the gravy.
老天  我...
Oh, man. I...
见到你很荣幸
What an honor to meet you.
我是特斯拉车和太空探索技术公司的粉丝
I'm-I'm such a fan of Tesla and SpaceX.
他还是Paypal[知名第三方在线支付公司]
以及SolarCity[专门发展家用光伏发电项目的公司]的CEO
你所有公司我都爱
All your companies.
加州理工的霍华德·沃罗威茨
Howard Wolowitz, Caltech.
很高兴认识你  霍华德
Nice to meet you, Howard.
来这里帮助不幸的人  感觉不错吧
Feels great to come down here and help the less fortunate, huh?
是的
Oh, yeah.
助人为乐的感觉最棒了
Nothing better than helping people.
我意识到这点时
Which is something I realized
是在遥远的外太空
when I was viewing Earth
当时我从国际空间站的甲板上瞭望地球
from the deck of the International Space Station,
我以科学宇航员的身份待了两个月
where I spent two months as a payload specialist,
这份工作我完全能胜任
a job I was qualified for
因为我是麻省理工培养出来的工程师
because I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
我浇的肉汁得再厚也没你的脸皮厚
And I thought I ladled the gravy on thick.
抱歉  只是...
Sorry. It's just...
你真是太了不起了
you're you, you know?
我超希望你能收养我
And I really want you to adopt me.
你在感恩节能出现在这里
Well, you're here on Thanksgiving,
所以你应该是个好人
so you're probably a good person.
我还让我老婆一起来了呢
Oh. I made my wife come down, too.
你觉得你会再次回到外太空吗
You think you might ever get back out to space?
这是工作邀请吗  因为我真的很想去火星
Is that a job offer? 'Cause I really want to go to Mars.
前提是能带上我老婆
Assuming I can bring my wife.
她完全不占地方
She hardly takes up any room.
基本就手提行李大小
She's basically a carry-on.
我们现在还没到那步
Well, we're not quite there yet,
但我们一直在寻找工程师
but we're always looking for engineers.
我把邮箱告诉你  我们保持联系
So let me give you my e-mail. We can stay in touch.
谢谢
Thank you.
瞧
Oh, look.
有人的南瓜派几乎没怎么吃
Someone hardly touched their pumpkin pie.
你想跟我一起吃吗
Want to share it with me?
跟埃隆·马斯克在收容所
A-a partially eaten piece of pumpkin pie
一起分享
from a homeless shelter?
被吃过的南瓜派  我当然愿意
With Elon Musk, you bet I do!
以一个在水族馆餐厅里的
You know, for a Thanksgiving buffet
感恩节自助餐来说  刚才那顿也太差了
in an aquarium cafeteria, that was really bad.
你就是在气他们移民帽发完了
You're just upset 'cause they ran out of Pilgrim hats.
他们还发给那孩子一顶  他在睡觉要来干嘛
They gave one to that baby. He wasn't even awake.
逢年过节怎么少得了你跟孩子上火生气呢
Well, it wouldn't be a holiday without you being mad at a baby.
想不想跟我玩一个我发明的海洋主题游戏
Would you care to play an ocean-themed game I invented?
当然  什么游戏
Sure. What is it?
游戏叫作"食物  朋友  战斗"
It's called Food, Friend, Fight.
我们中一人选出三种水生生物
One of us chooses three aquatic creatures,
然后另一人必须决定分别把什么当食物
and the other one must decide which he would eat,
做朋友  还是与之战斗
befriend, or battle.
就像"接吻  结婚  杀掉"
So it's like Kiss, Marry, Kill.
那是什么东西
What is that?
那是一个游戏  一方说出三个人
It's a game where you're given three people
另一方选择要跟谁接吻  结婚  杀掉
and you choose which one you'd kiss, marry, or kill.
我的游戏更好  不用跟人结婚
Well, my game is better, 'cause instead of marrying someone,
还可以吃掉他们
you get to eat them.
我们开始玩吧
Let's just play.
开始来点简单的
I'll start you off easy.
电鳗  河豚  虾
Electric eel, pufferfish, shrimp.
我不会跟电鳗战斗
Well, I wouldn't fight the eel,
因为我知道它产出的电流可以电死一匹马
because I know it can generate enough current to kill a horse.
所以我吃掉电鳗
So I'd eat the eel,
与虾战斗
fight the shrimp,
然后与河豚交友
and befriend the pufferfish,
因为我觉得自己水肿的日子里
because it would be nice to have company
有个同病相怜的伙伴挺好的
on those days I feel bloated.
答得漂亮
Very well done.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的  到你了
Okay, your turn.
海豹
Hmm. Seal,
盲鳗
hagfish...
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants.
我想跟海绵宝宝做朋友  但它不是真的
Well, I'd befriend SpongeBob but he's not real,
所以我做不到  是不是
so I can't do that, can I?
难道你可以跟盲鳗称兄道弟吗
But you can pal around with a hagfish?
不要挑刺好吗
Hey, let's not pull at that thread.
好的  我选择跟海绵宝宝战斗
Okay. I'll fight SpongeBob,
因为他非常友善
because he's so friendly
最后我们就变成互相挠痒痒了
we'll just end up tickling each other.
我会跟海豹做朋友
Um, I'll befriend the seal,
因为它们可以被人训练
because he's trainable, which is the problem
而我现在的朋友们正好有这问题
I'm having with my current friends.
意味着我只能吃掉盲鳗了
Which means I'll have to eat the hagfish.
不恶心吗  盲鳗一分钟内
Isn't that gross? I mean, a hagfish can produce
就可以产出一水桶粘液
enough mucus to fill a bucket in a minute.
我知道  它自带肉汁  非常顺口
I know. It makes its own gravy-- it'll slide right down.
我怀念这样
I miss this.
你怎么能怀念一个
How can you miss a game
你从来没玩过的游戏  小傻瓜
you've never played before, silly?
或许有时我就是这么傻吧
I guess sometimes I'm silly.
你去哪了  我看不出来火鸡烤没烤好
Hey. Where'd you go? I can't tell if the turkey's done!
马上来
Be right there!
你好啊  爱人
Hi, lover.
你这是闹哪样啊
What are you doing?
抱歉看了你日记  我想补偿你
I'm sorry about the journal. I want to make it up to you.
于是  我决定让你拍下我的耻辱照
So I'm gonna let you post
发到脸书上
a shame photo of me on Facebook.
我看了我老婆的日记
我这个淘气的胡萝卜
我才不会把那种东西发到网上
I am not putting that on the Internet!
我不想让大家看到这幅景象
I don't want people to see this.
连我都看不下去了
I don't want to see it!
你不想让大家看什么呀
Don't want people to see what, huh?
看这样吗
A little bit of this?
还是这样啊
Some of this?
既然今天是感恩节
And, since it's Thanksgiving,
那额外附赠这个
an extra helping of this?
感恩节...
Happy Thanks...
很开心你和艾米相处得愉快
I'm glad you had a nice time with Amy.
我也是  我们还能以朋友身份相处
Me, too. It's comforting to know
非常让人欣慰
that she and I are able to function as friends.
我跟前任从来当不来朋友
Well, I've never been friends with any of my exes.
我肯定你和莱纳德能当朋友
Oh, I'm sure you and Leonard will be able to pull it off.
是我的朋友艾米
Oh. It's my friend Amy.
你好
Hello.
好啊  谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
我刚从母亲家开车出来
I'm just driving home from my mother's.
你席间还愉快吗
Did you have a nice time?
愉快
I did. Um...
听着  我很喜欢今早我们一起相处的时光
Listen, I really enjoyed spending this morning with you.
不是我一个人的功劳
Well, I can't take all the credit.
那一条凤尾鱼游错方向的时候也很有趣
It was pretty funny when that one anchovy started going the wrong way.
确实
It was.
听着
Uh, listen,
我在考虑
I-I was thinking that, um,
我或许准备好重新做你女友了
maybe I'm ready to be your girlfriend again.
我以为我们只是朋友
I thought we were just friends.
我们是朋友
We are.
但我希望  也许...
But I was hoping, maybe...
艾米  我擅长很多事情
Amy, I excel at many things,
但忘记你并非其中一件事
but getting over you wasn't one of them.
我还是当你的朋友就好
I think I need to just be your friend.
好吧
Okay.
我理解
I understand.
好的
Good.
我看了盲鳗产粘液的视频
Oh, I watched a video of the hagfish producing mucus,
所以我要把答案改成吃海绵宝宝
so I'm gonna change my answer and eat SpongeBob.
好的  当然可以
Okay. Sure.